dhamaal.com 2015-03-26

# dhamaal

**Salient Points**

By visiting dhamaal.com you are accepting and agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. By using or continuing to use the site you agree to our use of your information (including sensitive personal information) in accordance with this Privacy Policy, as may be amended from time to time by dhamaal.com in its discretion. You also agree and consent to us collecting, storing, processing, transferring and sharing information (including sensitive personal information) related to you with third parties or service providers for the purposes as set out in this Privacy Policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**Collection of Information**

If you browse through this site without providing us with any personal information, we will gather and store some information about your visit, such as IP address, type of browser and operating system used, date and time you access our site, pages you visit, and if you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website. This information will not identify you personally and will not be linked back to you. 

Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature on the Website

The information we collect from customers helps us personalise and continually improve your shopping experience at dhamaal.com We use your information to assist sellers in handling orders, deliver products and services, process payments, communicate with you about orders, products, services and promotional offers, update our records and generally maintain your accounts with us, display content such as wish lists and customer reviews and recommend merchandise and services that might be of interest to you. We also use this information to improve our platform, prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our website and enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.

There will be times, such as when you submit an auto lead request to a dealer or fill out our contact form, when we will need to obtain personally identifiable information from you or about you. Such personally identifiable information may include your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and identification number. 

**Use and Sharing of Information**

At no time will we sell your personally-identifiable data without your permission unless set forth in this Privacy Policy. The information we receive about you or from you may be used by us or shared by us with our corporate affiliates, dealers, agents, vendors and other third parties to help process your request; to comply with any law, regulation, audit or court order; to help improve our website or the products or services we offer; for research; to better understand our customers' needs; to develop new offerings; and to alert you to new products and services (of us or our business associates) in which you may be interested. We may also combine information you provide us with information about you that is available to us internally or from other sources in order to better serve you. 

We may be required to share the aforesaid information with government authorities and agencies for the purposes of verification of identity or for prevention, detection, investigation including cyber incidents, prosecution and punishment of offences. You agree and consent for dhamaal.com to disclose your information, if so required under the applicable law.  

We do not share, sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties for unknown reasons.

**Cookies**

From time to time, we may place "cookies" on your personal computer. "Cookies" are small identifiers sent from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive, that help us to recognize you if you visit our website again. Also, our site uses cookies to track how you found our site. To protect your privacy we do not use cookies to store or transmit any personal information about you on the Internet. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies certain features of the site may not function property or at all as a result. 

**Additionally, you may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of the Website that are placed by third parties. We do not control the use of** **cookies by third parties.**

**Links**

Our website contains links to other sites. Such other sites may use information about your visit to this website. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to practices of such sites that we do not own or control or to people we do not employ. Therefore, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the accuracy or the integrity of the content included on such other sites. We encourage you to read the individual privacy statements of such websites.

**We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.**

**Security**

We safeguard your privacy using known security standards and procedures and comply with applicable privacy laws. Our websites combine industry-approved physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to ensure that your information is well protected though it's life cycle in our infrastructure.

Sensitive data is hashed or encrypted when it is stored in our infrastructure. Sensitive data is decrypted, processed and immediately re-encrypted or discarded when no longer necessary. We host web services in audited data centres, with restricted access to the data processing servers. Controlled access, recorded and live-monitored video feeds, 24/7 staffed security and biometrics provided in such data centres ensure that we provide secure hosting.

Use of dhamaal.com is available only to persons who can form a legally binding contract under the Indian Contract Act, 1872. If you are a minor i.e. under the age of 18 years, you may use dhamaal.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

**Opt-Out Policy**

Please email [support@dhamaal.com](mailto:support@dhamaal.com) if you no longer wish to receive any information from us. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically.

**Questions**

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please e-mail your questions to us at [support@dhamaal.com](mailto:support@dhamaal.com)
